English

[English \[AU\]](https://www.banklesstimes.com/au/)[English \[CA\]](https://www.banklesstimes.com/ca/privacy-policy/)[Dansk](https://www.banklesstimes.com/da/privatlivspolitik/)[Español](https://www.banklesstimes.com/es/politica-de-privacidad/)[Français](https://www.banklesstimes.com/fr/politique-de-confidentialite/)[Italiano](https://www.banklesstimes.com/it/politica-sulla-riservatezza/)[Nederlands \[NL\]](https://www.banklesstimes.com/nl/privacybeleid/)[Norsk](https://www.banklesstimes.com/no/personvernerklaering/)[Polski](https://www.banklesstimes.com/pl/polityka-prywatnosci/)[Português \[PT\]](https://www.banklesstimes.com/pt/politica-de-privacidade/)[Svenska](https://www.banklesstimes.com/se/integritetspolicy/)[English \[GB\]](https://www.banklesstimes.com/uk/privacy-policy/)

[Home](https://www.banklesstimes.com/)Privacy Policy

Why trust us

Advertiser Disclosure

Privacy Policy
==============

Amala Pillai

February 16th, 2023

Why trust us

Advertiser Disclosure

#### Introduction

Bankless Times is fully committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.

#### Personal Information

Bankless Times does not collect or save any personal information.Bankless Times does not use forms and all emails are completely deleted once they have been handled.

We do not place cookies on the computers of visitors to our site.

We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason.

We do not maintain any databases storing any personal information about our visitors.

Since we do not maintain any personal information about our visitors, we will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about this site.

#### Aggregate Information

Bankless Times uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is used to enable us to improve and expand the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site.

Bankless Times does not provide any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site.

#### Advertising

Bankless Times runs Google AdSense advertisements to help support the site. Google AdSense may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when providing advertisements to our site. This technology will send them information such as your IP address, your ISP, the browser you are using to visit our site, and possibly other information. This is generally used to help them target AdSense ads to you based on your geographic location or based on your interests according on your browsing history.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies by altering your browser settings or by managing settings in your internet security program. This can, however, affect how you are able to interact with some websites. This may include requiring you to manually login each time you visit ecommerce sites, forums, as well as certain other sites.

AdSense advertisements are provided by Google and are governed by their privacy policy which is available at the Google website.

Bankless Times does not have access to any of the information collected by Google.

#### External Web Links

Bankless Times contains in excess of thirty thousand links to external news web sites.

Once a Bankless Times user clicks on one of these external links, they have left theBankless Times web site. The privacy policy ofBankless Times no longer applies.

Some of these web sites may have privacy policies which differ from those ofBankless Times and which users may find to be unsatisfactory.Bankless Times takes no responsibility for the privacy policies of these sites. It is strictly the responsibility of the user to examine the suitability of their privacy policies.

### Contributors

###### [Amala Pillai](https://www.banklesstimes.com/author/amala/)

Senior Content Editor

Amala is custom content and news editor based in London. She is a former financial journalist based in Singapore with 7 years of experience covering a range of business and financial topics. Now she focuses on crypto and macro-economics. She has also covered feature profiles, tech, business politics and ESG— she was the Environment Editor for the Solutions Newspaper, 2016 and worked in an editorial capacity at both News corp (Dow Jones) and JBN. She also has experience as a content creator, strategist and brand editor for various financial institutions and banks.

Amala is custom content and news editor based in London. She is a former financial journalist based in Singapore with 7 years of experience covering a range of business and financial topics. Now she focuses on crypto and macro-economics. She has also covered feature profiles, tech, business politics and ESG— she was the Environment Editor for the Solutions Newspaper, 2016 and worked in an editorial capacity at both News corp (Dow Jones) and JBN. She also has experience as a content creator, strategist and brand editor for various financial institutions and banks.

Share

Latest price

BTC/USD

Cryptocurrency Guides

Invest in Cryptocurrencies

Buy Cryptocurrency

Business

More Reviews & Guides

Follow us

About Us

Since launching in 2012, Bankless Times is dedicated to bringing you the latest news and informational content within the alternative finance industry. Our news coverage spans the whole crypto-sphere so you’ll always stay up to date — be it on cryptocurrencies, NFTs, ICOs, Fintech, or Blockchain.

Advertising Disclaimer

Please be aware that some of the links on this site will direct you to the websites of third parties, some of whom are marketing affiliates and/or business partners of this site and/or its owners, operators and affiliates. We may receive financial compensation from these third parties. Notwithstanding any such relationship, no responsibility is accepted for the conduct of any third party nor the content or functionality of their websites or applications. A hyperlink to or positive reference to or review of a broker or exchange should not be understood to be an endorsement of that broker or exchange’s products or services. Risk Warning: Investing in digital currencies, stocks, shares and other securities, commodities, currencies and other derivative investment products (e.g. contracts for difference (“CFDs”) is speculative and carries a high level of risk. Each investment is unique and involves unique risks. CFDs and other derivatives are complex instruments and come with a high risk of losing money rapidly due to leverage. You should consider whether you understand how an investment works and whether you can afford to take the high risk of losing your money. Cryptocurrencies can fluctuate widely in prices and are, therefore, not appropriate for all investors. Trading cryptocurrencies is not supervised by any EU regulatory framework. Past performance does not guarantee future results. Any trading history presented is less than 5 years old unless otherwise stated and may not suffice as a basis for investment decisions. Your capital is at risk. When trading in stocks your capital is at risk. Past performance is not an indication of future results. Trading history presented is less than 5 years old unless otherwise stated and may not suffice as a basis for investment decisions. Prices may go down as well as up, prices can fluctuate widely, you may be exposed to currency exchange rate fluctuations and you may lose all of or more than the amount you invest. Investing is not suitable for everyone; ensure that you have fully understood the risks and legalities involved. If you are unsure, seek independent financial, legal, tax and/or accounting advice. This website does not provide investment, financial, legal, tax or accounting advice. Some links are affiliate links. For more information please read our full risk warning and disclaimer.

Copyright © 2024 - All Rights Reserved
